candytech.in 2019-12-28

# Privacy Policy | Candytech

### Privacy Policy

At [Candytech.in](https://candytech.in/), the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information received and collected by https://www.candytech.in and how it is used.

#### Do We Sell Anything?  No.

Disclosure* – Candytech.in is a Tech News website, and we **don’t sell anything** either online or offline. If you come across any similar brand name, it is not us. In fact, in case you have brought any products with Candytech brand name and have any queries please connect to the website candytech.co.in. 

#### Affiliate Partnerships

We have an affiliate partnership with Flipkart and Amazon, so you may see text links or Ads from our partner Web sites. If you find any irrelevant or low-quality product, you can report to us for its removal. We may earn a little commission when you buy products from Amazon or Flipkart using our links. 

Our editorial recommendations are not impacted by any of the affiliate partners in any manner. Also, we test most of the products before promotions for all quality checks so you don’t get a low-quality product recommendation.

#### **Reviews and Products**

Candytech doesn’t take sponsorship from companies to praise products. Companies may send us products for review on a returnable or give away basis, but that does not influence our editorials. Our opinion is neutral for all products/brands in last 4 years and will continue to do so.

Moreover, we value our readers and our reputation much more than monetary benefits.

#### **Sponsored Posts**

We receive several emails daily for sponsored content and guest posts for links. Till date, we have not entertained any such request nor we will do it in future. We don’t provide any backlinks or engage in any such activity.

#### Cookies and Web Beacons

www.candytech.in does use cookies to store information about a visitor’s preferences, record user-specific information from pages the user accesses, customize webpage content based on a visitor’s browser type or other information that a visitor sends via his or her browser. 

#### **Log Files  **

Like many other Web sites, http://www.candytech.in makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and the number of clicks to analyze trends and analytics. The IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

#### **DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on http://www.candytech.in. Besides, Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to http://www.candytech.in and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners **(Google)** may use cookies and web beacons on our site. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at kanuj@candytech.in

Author: Kanuj 

Published On 06-02-2018
